upcity.com 2014-11-21

# SEO Software from UpCity | Inbound Marketing for Small Business & Agencies

## Privacy Policy

This is the web site of UpCity LLC, a provider of [SEO Software](http://upcity.com/)

Our postal address is:

372 W. Ontario, Suite 301  
Chicago, IL, 60654

We can be reached via e-mail at [info@upcity.com](mailto:info@upcity.com) or you can reach us via the see contact page.

This Privacy Policy describes the information UpCity, LLC ("UpCity") may collect about you through your use of the UpCity search engine optimization service and related web sites (collectively, the "UpCity Site"). It also describes how UpCity uses your information, how UpCity protects it, and what choices you have on how that information is used.

### Information Collection and Use by UpCity

UpCity collects and uses information voluntarily submitted by a user, such as a user's name, email address, URLs, keywords, and credit card payment information, in connection with the services provided by UpCity on behalf of such user. UpCity may also share such information with its affiliated companies and business partners (such as agents or subcontractors) who are acting on UpCity's behalf to support your customer relationship with UpCity, unless otherwise agreed by you or required by law.

UpCity may also log non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the UpCity Site. This data is used to manage the UpCity Site, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to visitors. User IP addresses may also be recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

UpCity may also use a user's email address to send updates, such as a newsletter or news regarding UpCity's products and services. Users may choose not to receive email of this type by clicking an "opt out" link located at the bottom of the update.

Unless otherwise agreed by you or required by law, information collected by UpCity may be (i) used by UpCity for marketing and business purposes, (ii) retained by UpCity indefinitely, and (iii) sold or otherwise transmitted to third parties.

### Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Systems

UpCity may use cookies or other similar tracking means to store user's preferences and to record session information. UpCity may link the information it stores in its tracking systems to any personally identifiable information you submit while on the UpCity Site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some tracking systems, or notify you when a tracking systems is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your tracking system preferences -- however, you may have to enable tracking systems from UpCity in order to use some functions on the UpCity Site.

### Links

The UpCity Site may contain links to other sites. UpCity is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on the UpCity Site.

### Sharing and Disclosure of Information UpCity Collects

In addition to the disclosures otherwise described in this privacy statement, UpCity may disclose personal information to a third party if UpCity believes that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by UpCity, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the UpCity Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of UpCity's products and services. UpCity reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of UpCity or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below.

### Changes in Our Privacy Policy

From time to time UpCity may make changes to its privacy policy. If UpCity makes changes, it will post them on the UpCity Site so users will be aware of what information UpCity collects, how UpCity uses it, and when UpCity may disclose it. A user is bound by any changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted. If, however, UpCity is going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection it will notify you by posting a notice on the UpCity Site for 30 days.

### Contacting UpCity

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of the UpCity Site, or your dealings with the UpCity Site, please contact us at: [info@upcity.com](mailto:info@upcity.com).

Want to learn more about the UpCity solution? [Try It Out](https://upcity.com/signup) today!

Wondering how well your website is doing with SEO? Get a Free SEO Report!
